trafficjunky.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy | TrafficJunky

## 1\. Application of This Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to TrafficJunky only. It will tell you how and why we gather and use information about you while acting as a business advertiser. TrafficJunky Inc. understands the importance of  privacy and uses best practices, to uphold this while using our website within a business to business relationship context. Below is our privacy policy that ensures you are protected while using TrafficJunky. Please contact our support team if you have any further questions regarding this policy.

## 2\. Collection and Our Use of Your Information

TrafficJunky collects your name, email address, and other important information provided by you in order to provide any services requested. In addition, we collect credit card, and bank information from purchases made through TrafficJunky. In the course of using our site, we automatically log information such as IP address, browser type, referrer and other technical data for internal use only. This information is used to optimize our website's technical usability and for internal research data. In addition, you hereby agree to receive from us promotional or services related communications which may contain sexually explicit content through emails or other means. We also collect and use your data for the purpose of distributing our opt-in newsletters and to send promotions. Users can remove themselves through the unsubscribe link at the bottom of all emails or contact us.

You authorize TrafficJunky, directly or through third parties, to make any inquiries we consider necessary to validate your identity. This may include asking you for further information that will allow us to reasonably identify you, requiring you to take steps to confirm ownership of your email address or financial instruments or verifying your Information against third party databases or through other sources. We may also ask to see your driver’s licence or other government issued picture ID or any other identifying documents at any time. TrafficJunky reserves the right to close, suspend, or limit access to your account in the event we are unable to obtain or verify this information.

**_California Consumer Privacy Act Notice_**

As of January 1, 2020, the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“ **CCPA** ”) provides California residents (“ **Consumer(s)** ”) certain rights with respect to their personal information, as this term is defined under the CCPA. In addition to the rights we state under this policy and subject to the exceptions found under the CCPA, Consumers have the right to:

  * Opt-out of the sale of their personal information, should we sell their personal information;
  * Be informed of certain information concerning our collection and use of their personal information;
  * Request that we delete certain personal information we collected from them;
  * Appoint an agent to exercise their rights provided for by the CCPA, provided that a duly executed notarized power of attorney is presented and provided that the agent has information deemed sufficient to allow us to verify the  identity of the Consumer in question and to locate his/her information in our systems;
  * Not be subjected to discrimination for the exercise of these rights. We will not deny California residents the use of our service, neither will we provide a different level or quality or services for exercising any of their CCPA rights, unless as permitted under the CCPA.

This Website does not sell nor has it sold in the past 12 months personal information to third parties for monetary or other valuable considerations. We may however disclose certain personal information with third parties, service providers and entities within our corporate group in order to enable them to perform certain services on our behalf and namely to make the Website work properly. Regardless, we respect the California residents’ right to exclude personal information from such sharing arrangements and to thereby opt-out of any future sale of their personal information.

## If the CCPA is applicable to you and you would like to record such preference, please click on the following link for “[Do Not Sell My Personal Information](mailto:privacy@managemydata.eu?subject=Do%20Not%20Sell%20My%20Personal%20Information)”.

## 3\. Disclosure of Your Information

TrafficJunky DOES NOT rent or sell any personal information provided by you or about you to any third party without your permission. We do disclose information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we DO NOT disclose to any entity any information that could be used to identify you personally. Certain information, such as your password, credit card number, and bank information, will not be disclosed in aggregate at all. except that we may release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our terms and conditions and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of TrafficJunky, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## 4\. Reviewing and Changing Your Personally Identifiable Information

Upon creating an account, you will be able to review and change your information through TrafficJunky. This is accomplished by logging in to your account and clicking on the "My Account" tab. From there, you can update individual information provided by you regarding your account. To reduce the occurrence of unauthorized access to your account information, TrafficJunky strongly urges you to periodically change your password. Upon request, TrafficJunky will remove your credit card or any other information from our system. To make this request, contact our support team. TrafficJunky will keep information in our files, including credit card information, that you have requested to remove only in some circumstances, such as to comply with Federal and State Law, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, comply with Merchant Banking and Association Agreements, reduce fraud, enhance security, and to enforce our Terms of Use Agreement

## 5\. Cookies and Session Management

This site uses cookies for session management. We also use form and URL elements that may contain a unique user ID. Cookies, form elements and other related management techniques are used to ensure a continuous user session.

## 6\. Security

TrafficJunky has security measures in place to protect and prevent the misuse and loss of the information under our control. We use industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information. Our technical experts at TrafficJunky work hard to ensure your secure use of our services.

## 7\. Children

Minors in the country, province or state in which they live, can only use this Site with the approval of a parent or guardian.

## 8\. Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may change this policy as new services are added or old ones are changed. Such changes will be effective when a notice of the change is posted on the Site. Please check this Privacy Policy from time to time for updates by checking the date of the "Last Update" at the top of this document. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our policies and terms of use, but you should check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. As we continue to develop our business, we might reorganize or transfer our business units or assets. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice unless the user consents otherwise. Also, in the unlikely event that TrafficJunky or substantially all of its assets are acquired, user information be one of the transferred assets.

## 9\. International Payment Processing

MG Freesites Ltd. Block 1, 195-197 Old Nicosia-Limassol Road Dali Industrial Zone Nicosia, 2540 Cyprus, VAT # CY 10243057K
